airgorilla.com 2016-01-28

# AirGorilla Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for AirGorilla. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

5\. Third party ads and user behavior.

### Section 1: Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We do not sell, or otherwise allow your email address or other personal information to be used by other companies for advertising or other purposes. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to validate a reservation properly or ship an order. For instance, you cannot book an airline reservation without the airline knowing your name. As an alternate example, Federal Express would need to know your address if an airline ticket is to be shipped to your door. If you send us correspondence, including email and faxes, we may retain such information to measure and improve our customer service, or to investigate potential fraud. 

**Web Routing Data:** Because of the way that World Wide Web communication standards work, when you arrive at or leave the AirGorilla Web site, we automatically receive the Web address of the site that you came from or are going to. We also collect information on which pages of our Web site you visit while you are on the AirGorilla site, the type of browser you use and the times you access our Web site. We use this information only to try to understand our customers' preferences better and to manage the load on our servers, so as to improve our service and your experience with AirGorilla. We do not track the Web sites that you visit before or after you leave the AirGorilla site.

**Cookies:** "Cookies" are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as an AirGorilla customer if you return to the AirGorilla site using the same computer and browser. We send a "session cookie" to your computer if and when you log in to our site. These cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session. Once you log out or close your browser, these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect.

### Section 2: Opt-in Lists

From time to time we may offer optional questionnaires or surveys to our clients in an effort to improve our services. The use of the information we collect will be clearly stated in the questionnaire or survey, and the client will be given the option to participate or not in the questionnaire or survey.

We may at some time in the future offer email opt-in newsletters or specials. Our clients will be given the opportunity to sign up for these offers; and if they should choose to participate, they will have the option of canceling the offer at any time.  
  
**Spam Policy** As a customer of AirGorilla we may be sending you an introductory email newsletter. We value your privacy and time and will not send you another email if you simply opt out by clicking the "OPT OUT" button prominently displayed on this newsletter. We realize your time is valuable, so we are sending this newsletter to selected customers no more than once a month. This newsletter will contain travel tips, valuable coupons, and specials that will save you money. In addition from time to time we will be including Give-Aways and free gifts. We do not share our customer email list with other companies and you will only receive our newsletter on an infrequent basis. Again, if you do not wish to receive our tips, news and offers, simply opt out. We abide strictly by the requirements of the CAN SPAM Act of 2003.

### Section 3: Inventory or Modification of Data

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website and at the end of this privacy policy document:

* See what data we have about you, if any.  
* Change/correct any data we have about you.  
* Have us delete any data we have about you.  
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Section 4: Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. Logically, if you use one of our pages that does not process personal information, such as a simple list of fares or our simple home page, you will not see a lock symbol or "https," since there is no reason such a page would ever require a secure socket layer (SSL).

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

### Section 5: Fraud Screening

We will use card authorization and fraud screening services to verify that your card information and address match, and that the card has not been reported as lost or stolen.

### Section 6: Revision of Policy

This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the AirGorilla site or as we incorporate suggestions from our customers.

### Section 7: Spam Policy.

As a customer of AirGorilla we may be sending you an introductory email newsletter. We value your privacy and time and will not send you another email if you simply opt out by clicking the "OPT OUT" button prominently displayed on this newsletter. We realize your time is valuable, so we are sending this newsletter to selected customers no more than once a month. This newsletter will contain travel tips, valuable coupons, and specials that will save you money. In addition from time to time we will be including Give-Aways and free gifts. We do not share our customer email list with other companies and you will only receive our newsletter on an infrequent basis. Again, if you do not wish to receive our tips, news and offers, simply opt out. We abide strictly by the requirements of the CAN SPAM Act of 2003.

### Section 8: Third Party Ads and User Behavior

On various pages of this site, we display third-party ads from Google, Yahoo, and other sources. If you click on one of these ads, you instantly enter their proprietary servers where you are subject to the third party's own privacy policy. They frequently monitor user behavior in order to figure out what topics of ads you might appreciate to see in the future on further web sites you visit. Therefore they will retain data on your behavior and, by extension, your interests.

### Section 9: Addendum - Travel Ad Network Advertising Cookies

This site has contracted with Travel Ad Network (publisher@traveladnetwork.com) and its third party ad-serving technology provider Atlas, a Microsoft Corporation Subsidiary, to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', advertisement impressions, and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, Travel Ad Network may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by Travel Ad Network, please see Travel Ad Network's privacy policy at the first of two links below. Cookies are important devices for both serving more relevant ads to users and measuring advertising effectiveness. You may opt out of accepting cookies at any time by clicking these links:

To opt out of travelad.net, go to   
http://www.traveladnetwork.com/content/view/56/79/  
To opt out of Atlas (Microsoft Advertising), go to   
http://www.atlassolutions.com/optout.aspx

### Section 10: Compliance to Policy

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 619 435-2147 or[](http://www.airgorilla.com/agemail.html)for email.
